Guide to the Suzanne Comhaire-Sylvain Papers M1835
Department of Special Collections and University Archives
- Series 5: Maps
  - Republica de Haiti esquema de promedio annual de lluvia y distribucion de poblacion (Servicio tecnico de mineria y geologia. Estados Unidos de Venezuela, Ministerio de Fomento ) (Flat-box 19, Item 14)
  - Carte physique, politique et economique de la Republique d' Haiti (American Map Co INC. New York) (Flat-box 19, Item 15)
- Series 6: Miscellaneous publications
  This series includes additional newspaper clippings, book reviews, and publication by and about Suzanne Comhaire-Sylvain and her family.
  - Publications on Haiti 1938-1995 (Box 9, Folder 3)
  - Publications on Haiti 1933-1986 (Box 9, Folder 4)
  - Miscellaneous newspaper articles, book reviews, notes (Box 9, Folder 5)
  - Miscellaneous paperwork from university (Box 9, Folder 6)